(Sheldon:)I'm just talking about bees.
(Sheldon:)They're on The Discovery Channel.
(Sheldon:)What are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)Bees.
[GASPS]
(Penny:)I just got that physicist joke.
- Gee, Penny, thanks for buying us dinner.
PENNY: Mm-hm.
- Yeah, what's the occasion?
- No occasion.
(Penny:)Just felt like getting some Chinese chow
for my peeps.
(Sheldon:)Did you remember to ask for the chicken
to be diced not shredded?
(Sheldon:)Even though the menu
specifies shredded?
Brown rice, not white? Stop at the grocery
and get the mustard?
(Sheldon:)Pick up the low-sodium soy sauce
from the market?
(Leonard(into phone):)Good.
(Sheldon:)See how it's done, Leonard?
What do we got going on tonight?
Playing Halo? Watching Battlestar?
Drop some Mentos in Diet Coke?
You wanna watch Battlestar?